realestate.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Zillow Group

  * Terms of Use 
  * Privacy Policy 
  * Privacy Policy (Effective Jan. 1, 2020) 
  * Government and Civil Information Requests 

**Last Updated** : 10/2/2019

Welcome and thank you for your interest in Zillow (operated by Zillow, Inc. and its affiliates, collectively, “Zillow Group”). By clicking a registration or new account submission button, or by otherwise using Zillow Group’s websites, networks, mobile applications, or other services provided by Zillow Group (collectively, the “Services”), or accessing any content provided by Zillow Group through the Services, you agree to be bound by the following terms of use, as updated from time to time (“Terms of Use”).

  1. **Zillow Group’s Role**. ZILLOW, INC. DOES NOT, AND THE SERVICES ARE NOT INTENDED TO, PROVIDE FINANCIAL OR REAL ESTATE ADVICE. ZILLOW, INC. IS NOT A LENDER OR REAL ESTATE BROKER REPRESENTING YOU OR ANOTHER USER. FOR ADDITIONAL INFORMATION, SEE SECTION 9. Zillow Group’s business is primarily funded through advertising. You understand and agree that the Services may include advertisements, and that these are necessary to support the Services. To help make the advertisements relevant and useful to you, Zillow Group may serve advertisements based on the information we collect through the Services. See the [Privacy Policy](https://www.zillow.com/corp/Privacy.htm) for more details. Zillow, Inc. has a real estate broker license in certain states (see Section 22), but Zillow Group does not: (a) act as a real estate agent for you or any other user; (b) represent you or another user in the purchase, sale or exchange of real property, including any negotiation thereof; or (c) lease or rent, offer to lease or rent, or negotiate the lease of real property or otherwise aid or assist in the lease of real property. Zillow Group assumes no responsibility for any result or consequence related directly or indirectly to any action or inaction that consumers take based on the Services or any other information available through or in connection with the Services.
  2. **Zillow Group’s Brands and Businesses**. Zillow Group operates the following brands; any use of any of the Services provided by the following brands is subject to these Terms of Use: (a) Zillow; (b) Trulia; (c) HotPads; (d) StreetEasy; (e) Naked Apartments; (f) Out East; (g) Bridge Interactive Group;  (h) Zillow Group Marketplace; and (i) Mortech. Services offered by  
Zillow Home Loans, LLC (“ZHL”) and Zillow Closing Services, LLC are not subject to these Terms of Use.
  3. **Referrals**. While you are not responsible for making referral payments to Zillow, as part of the Services, Zillow may be paid valuable consideration in exchange for your referral to a real estate professional (“Real Estate Referral”). You authorize Zillow to make such Real Estate Referral and acknowledge Zillow may be paid valuable consideration for facilitating such referral. Additionally, as part of the Services, you may be referred to Zillow Group’s affiliate, ZHL (a “Mortgage Referral”). ZHL provides mortgage loan origination services. Because of this relationship, Zillow Group may receive a financial or other benefit from a Mortgage Referral.
  4. **Eligibility;** **Accounts and Registration**. You must be at least 18 years of age to use the Service. By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you represent and warrant that: (a) you are at least 18 years of age; (b) you have not previously been suspended or removed from the Services; and (c) your registration and your use of the Services is in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations. To access some features of the Services, you may be required to register for an account. When you register for an account, you may be required to provide us with some information about yourself, such as email address or other contact information. You agree that the information you provide is accurate and that you will keep it accurate and up-to-date at all times. When you register, you may be asked to provide a password. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password, and you are responsible for all actions taken via your account. You may not share your user account(s) with others. Unless you have entered into a commercial agreement with Zillow Group permitting you to use the Services for transactions on behalf of another person, you may only use the Services for transactions on your own behalf, and not on behalf of any other person.
  5. **Use of the Services; Restrictions.**
    1. **Use of the Services**. As long as you comply with these Terms of Use, Zillow Group grants you a non-exclusive, limited, revocable, personal, non-transferable license to use the Services, and to download and use any App (as defined in Section 5(B) below) on your mobile device in object code form, for your personal use. If you are a real estate or mortgage professional acting in your professional capacity, you may additionally use the Services to provide information, to the extent permitted by applicable law, to your clients and to take actions on behalf of your clients (“Pro Use”). If you use the Services for a Pro Use, you represent and warrant that you have obtained all required authorizations and consents from your client.  Except as expressly stated herein, these Terms of Use do not provide you with a license to use, reproduce, distribute, display or provide access to any portion of the Services on third-party web sites or otherwise. The Services may include software for use in connection with the Services. The Services may not be used for transactions in commercial real estate, which includes, without limitation, commercially zoned properties and vacation rentals.
    2. **Mobile Applications.** To use any mobile application feature of the Services (each, an “App”), you must have a compatible mobile device. Zillow Group does not warrant that any App will be compatible with your mobile device. You may use mobile data in connection with an App and may incur additional charges from your wireless provider for using an App. You agree that you are solely responsible for any applicable charges. Zillow Group may update any app and may automatically electronically update the version of any App that you have installed on a mobile device. You consent to all automatic upgrades, and understand that these Terms of Use will apply to all updated versions of an App. Any third-party open source software included in an App is subject to the applicable open source license and may be available directly from the creator under an open source license. These Terms of Use do not apply to your use of software obtained from a third-party source under an open source license.
    3. **Use of Content**. Subject to the restrictions set forth in these Terms of Use, you may copy information from the Services only as necessary for your personal use or Pro Use to view, save, print, fax and/or e-mail such information. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the aggregate level data provided on the [Zillow Local-Info Pages](http://www.zillow.com/local-info/), and available at <http://www.zillowblog.com/research/> (the “Aggregate Data”) may be used for non-personal uses, e.g., real estate market analysis. You may display and distribute derivative works of the Aggregate Data (e.g., within a graph), so long as Zillow Group is cited as a source on every page where the Aggregate Data is displayed, including “Data Provided by Zillow Group” or similar language. Such cite may not include a Zillow Group logo without Zillow Group’s prior written approval or imply any relationship between you and Zillow Group beyond Zillow being a source of the Aggregate Data.
  6. **Prohibited Use**. BY USING THE SERVICES, YOU AGREE NOT TO: 
    * use information provided by Zillow Group through the Services in making any loan-related decisions;
    * reproduce, modify, distribute, display or otherwise provide access to, create derivative works from, decompile, disassemble, or reverse engineer any portion of the Services, except as explicitly permitted under these Terms of Use;
    * provide/post/authorize a link to any of the Services (including but not limited to an agent profile page) from a third-party website that is not a real estate-related website owned or operated by a real estate or lending professional or institution;
    * remove or modify any copyright or other intellectual property notices that appear in the Services;
    * use the Services for resale, service bureau, time-sharing or other similar purposes;
    * use the Services in any way that is unlawful, or harms Zillow Group, its service providers, suppliers, or any other user;
    * distribute or post spam, chain letters, pyramid schemes, or similar communications through the Services;
    * impersonate another person or misrepresent your affiliation with another person or entity;
    * reproduce, publicly display, or otherwise make accessible on or through any other website, application, or service any reviews, ratings, and/or profile information about real estate, lending, or other professionals, underlying images of or information about real estate listings, or other data or content available through the Services, except as explicitly permitted by Zillow Group for a particular portion of the Services;
    * upload invalid data, viruses, worms, or other software agents to the Services;
    * interfere with, or compromise the system integrity or security of the Services, or otherwise bypass any measures Zillow Group may use to prevent or restrict access to the Services;
    * conduct automated queries (including screen and database scraping, spiders, robots, crawlers, bypassing “captcha” or similar precautions, and any other automated activity with the purpose of obtaining information from the Services) on the Services;
    * use any of Zillow Group’s trademarks without approval, including but not limited to using them as part of your business name, screen name or email address on the Services;
    * access or use any of the Services to develop competitive products or services; or
    * attempt to, or permit or encourage any third party to, do any of the above
  7. **Fees**. 
    1. **Generally**. You may be required to pay fees to access certain features of the Services. All fees are in U.S. dollars and are non-refundable. If Zillow Group changes the fees for all or part of the Services, including by adding fees or charges, Zillow Group will provide you advance notice of those changes. If you do not accept the changes, Zillow Group may discontinue providing the applicable part of the Services to you. Zillow Group’s authorized third-party payment processor will charge the payment method you specified at the time of purchase. You authorize Zillow Group to charge all fees as described in these Terms of Use for the Services you select to that payment method. If you pay any fees with a credit card, Zillow Group may seek pre-authorization of your credit card account before your purchase to verify that the credit card is valid and has the necessary funds or credit available to cover your purchase.
    2. **Subscriptions**. The Services may include features that allow for automatically recurring payments for periodic charges (“Subscription Service”). If you decide to activate a Subscription Service, you authorize Zillow Group to periodically charge, on a going-forward basis and until cancellation of either the recurring payments or your account, all accrued sums on or before the payment due date for the accrued sums. The subscription will continue unless and until you cancel your subscription, or we terminate it. You must cancel your Subscription Service before it renews in order to avoid billing of the next periodic subscription fee to your account. We will bill the periodic subscription fee to the payment method you provide to us during registration (or to a different payment method if you change your payment information). Zillow Group may change the subscription fee for any subsequent subscription period but will provide you advance notice of any increase before it applies. Unless otherwise stated in your product-specific agreement, you may cancel a Subscription Service by contacting us at consumercare@zillow.com, by contacting your business consultant, or through your settings page for the paid feature.

  8. **User Materials.**
    1. **UGC Definition; License Grant**. Certain portions of the Services may allow users to upload or otherwise provide to Zillow Group images, photos, video, data, text, listings and other content (“User Materials”). By uploading or otherwise providing User Materials to the Services, you grant Zillow Group an irrevocable, perpetual, royalty-free worldwide license to: (i) use, copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, modify, prepare derivative works of or incorporate into other works, and translate your User Materials, in connection with the Services, or in any other media; and (ii) sublicense these rights, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law. Zillow Group will not pay you for your User Materials or to exercise any rights related to your User Materials set forth in the preceding sentence. Zillow Group may remove or modify your User Materials at any time. You are solely responsible for all User Materials made through your user account(s) on the Services or that you otherwise make available through the Services. For all User Materials, you represent and warrant that you are the creator and owner of the User Materials, or have the necessary licenses, rights, consents, and permissions (including all permissions required under applicable privacy and intellectual property law) to authorize Zillow Group and other users to access and use your User Materials as necessary to exercise the licenses granted by you under these Terms of Use.  Zillow Group will not use client contact information that is uploaded by agents into the Zillow Agent Hub portal for any purpose.
    2. **UGC Disclaimer**. Zillow Group is under no obligation to edit or control your User Materials or the User Materials of any other User and will not be in any way responsible or liable for any User Materials. Zillow Group may, however, at any time and without prior notice, screen, remove, edit, or block any User Materials on the Services, including User Materials, that in Zillow Group’s sole judgment violate these Terms of Use or are otherwise objectionable, including in any way described in our Good Neighbor Policy described in Section 14(B). You understand that when using the Services, you may be exposed to User Materials of other users and acknowledge that User Materials may be inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable. You agree to waive, and do waive, any legal or equitable right or remedy you may have against Zillow Group with respect to User Materials. Zillow Group expressly disclaims any and all liability in connection with User Materials. If notified by a user or content owner that User Materials allegedly do not conform with these Terms of Use, Zillow Group may investigate the allegation and determine in Zillow Group’s sole discretion whether to remove the User Materials, which Zillow Group reserves the right to do at any time and without notice. For more information on Zillow Group’s handling of infringing content, please see Section 12 below.
  9. **Third-Party/Linked Services/Sent information.**
    1. **Generally**. The Services include links to third-party products, services and websites, as well as materials provided by third parties, and may include functionality that allows for the distribution of your User Materials or your personal information (collectively, your “User Information”) to third parties not under Zillow Group’s control (each, a “Third-Party Provider”). Third-Party Providers are solely responsible for their services. You are responsible for your use and submission of User Information to any third-party, and your dealings or business conducted with any third party arising in connection with the Services are solely between you and such third party. Your use of third-party sites, services, or products may be subject to associated third-party terms of use and privacy policies or other agreements, which you are solely responsible for complying with. Zillow Group does not endorse, and takes no responsibility for such products, services, Web sites, and materials, or a Third-Party Provider’s use of your User Information. By using a tool that allows for User Information to be transferred, you agree that Zillow Group may transfer the applicable User Information or other information to the applicable third-parties, which are not under the control of Zillow Group. If you submit a contact form or otherwise indicate your interest in contacting a Third-Party Provider, you may receive telemarketing calls from the Third-Party Provider using the contact information you provided. Third-Party Providers may keep your contact information and any other information received by the Third-Party Provider in processing a contact or other request form. Zillow Group is not responsible for any damages or costs of any type arising out of or in any way connected with your dealings with these third parties.
    2. **Certain Third-Party Services**. 
      1. _Non-Affiliated Financial Products_. If you choose to contact a non-affiliated bank, lender, financial institution, originator, loan broker, or other mortgage professional through the Services by filling out a contact, other request form or otherwise indicating your interest in contacting (or being contacted by) a Third-Party Provider (including requests for rate quotes) on the Services, you authorize Zillow Group, and Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc. in particular (and, in the event that the Third-Party Provider is a bank, lender, financial institution, originator, loan broker or other mortgage professional, each a “Lender,” you authorize Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc. in particular) to provide the information you submit to the Third-Party Provider. If you include your name, contact information and other information in a request, your identity will no longer be anonymous to the Third-Party Provider. Your submission of information and any request for quotes through the Services is not an application for credit. Zillow Group is only providing an administrative service to consumers and participating Lenders. Decisions regarding Lenders contacting consumers are made by participating Lenders and not Zillow Group. These non-binding quotes are not intended to be official Loan Estimates as defined in the Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act. By using these features, the disclosures and consent required under certain state laws are deemed to be provided, received, and agreed to. Interest rates displayed through the Services are for information purposes only and reflect non-binding customized quotes of the terms a Lender might offer a borrower fitting a consumer’s anonymous profile. Actual interest rates may vary. Loan approval standards are established and maintained solely by individual Lenders. Consumers should rely on their own judgment in deciding which available loan product, terms, and Third-Party Provider best suit their needs and financial means. Except for services offered by ZHL, Zillow Group: (a) is not a Lender, loan originator, loan processor or underwriter; (b) does not aid or assist borrowers in obtaining loans, solicit borrowers or Lenders for loans, offer or negotiate terms of loans; (c) does not take mortgage applications, make loans or credit decisions or pre-approve borrowers for loans; (d) is not an agent of either any consumer or any Lender; (e) does not endorse, refer or recommend any Third-Party Provider that pays Zillow Group or the products of any Third-Party Provider that pays Zillow; (f) is not responsible for any errors or delays caused by consumers or any Third-Party Provider in the loan process; and (g) does not guarantee offer of, or acceptance into, any particular loan program or specific loan terms, conditions, or rates with any Third-Party Provider, or that any rates or terms will be the best available.
      2. _Rental Products_. If you choose to submit your information in order to submit a background or credit check, you are subject to the Checkr and Experian terms as described in Section 9(C) below. Zillow Group does not process or store background or credit check information, and does not control how a landlord uses background or credit check information in evaluating its applications. Zillow Group does not guarantee any acceptance by a landlord of an application, but does require all landlords using the Services to comply with the Fair Housing Act and other applicable laws.
    3. **Additional Terms for Third-Party Services**. Certain aspects of the Services include third-party tools that are subject to additional third-party terms, including, but not limited to, the following: 
      1. **Windows Live Virtual Earth.** Windows Live Virtual Earth imagery is supplied by Microsoft Corporation, and use is subject to the Microsoft MapPoint Terms of Use available at <http://www.microsoft.com/maps/assets/docs/terms.aspx>.
      2. **Google Maps.** Some of the Services implement the Google Maps web mapping service. Your use of Google Maps is subject to Google’s terms of use, available at <http://www.google.com/intl/en_us/help/terms_maps.html>, and Google’s Privacy Policy, available at <https://www.google.com/intl/ALL/policies/privacy/index.html>.
      3. **Stripe.  **Some of the Services allow you to use Stripe Connect to make payments to other users, and may include additional processing or application fees detailed when you choose to connect to Stripe. Your use of Stripe is subject to the Stripe Connected Account Agreement, available at <https://stripe.com/us/connect-account/legal>. Additionally, by using Stripe, you agree not to use Stripe (and the Services generally) for any Prohibited Business purposes, as listed at <https://stripe.com/us/prohibited-businesses>.
      4. **Checkr**. Some of the Services allow users to use our third-party background check partner’s, Checkr’s, services to submit an application and background check to a landlord. If you are a Renter using the Checkr services, you authorize Zillow to obtain your background check report, including criminal and eviction history, and to share that information with Landlords you submit an application to, and agree to the Checkr Terms of Use available at: <https://checkr.com/terms-of-service/>. If you are a Landlord using the Checkr services, you agree to use the background check reports in compliance with law, and agree to the Checkr Background Check Report Terms of Use, available at: <https://zillow.com/rental-manager/terms/Checkr-Terms-of-Use>.
      5. **Plaid**. The rental payments feature allows you to link your bank account through Plaid for the purposes of making or receiving rental payments. By using Plaid, you agree to your personal and financial information being transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the Plaid Privacy Policy, available at <https://plaid.com/legal>.
      6. Some of the Services allow you to use the Experian Connect service to submit a request for a credit check be sent to a landlord. If you use the Experian services, you agree to the Experian Connect Terms and Conditions, available at <https://connect.experian.com/legal/terms.html>.

  10. **Intellectual Property.  **The Services are owned and operated by Zillow Group. The user interfaces, design, information, data, code, products, software, graphics, and all other elements of the Services (“Zillow Group Materials”) provided by Zillow Group are protected by intellectual property and other laws and are the property of Zillow Group or Zillow Group’s third-party licensors. Except as expressly allowed by these Terms of Use, you may not make use of the Zillow Group Materials, and Zillow Group reserves all rights to the Zillow Group Materials and Services not granted expressly in these Terms of Use.

_Intellectual Property Notices_ :

Certain content on the Services is owned by ZIP+4 data, United States Postal Service, and Yahoo! Inc. To view a complete list of our issued patents and active trademarks, click [here](https://www.zillow.com/corp/Terms/ip/). The names of actual companies, products, and services mentioned herein may be the trademarks of their respective owners. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved. Zillow Group does not assert copyright or grant any rights to the underlying images or descriptions of real estate listings provided through the Services. Any use of these images and descriptions is subject to the copyright owner’s permission and the requirements of applicable law.

  11. **Feedback.** If you choose to provide input and suggestions regarding the Services, including related to any Zillow Group Materials (“Feedback”), then you hereby grant Zillow Group an unrestricted, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive, fully-paid, royalty-free right to use the Feedback in any manner and for any purpose, including the improve the Services or create other products and services.
  12. **DMCA; Claims of Copyright Infringement.** Zillow Group respects the intellectual property rights of others, and asks that everyone using the Services do the same. Anyone who believes that their work has been reproduced on the Services in a way that constitutes copyright infringement may notify Zillow Group’s copyright agent in accordance with Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(c)(2), by providing the following information: 
    1. Identification of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;
    2. Identification of the material that you claim is infringing and needs to be removed, including a description of where it is located on the Services so that the copyright agent can locate it;
    3. Your address, telephone number, and, if available, e-mail address, so that the copyright agent may contact you about your complaint; and
    4. A signed statement that the above information is accurate; that you have a good faith belief that the identified use of the material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and, under penalty of perjury, that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf in this situation.

Notices of copyright infringement claims should be sent as follows:  
By mail:  
Zillow, Inc.  
1301 Second Avenue, Floor 31  
Seattle, WA 98101  
Attention: Copyright Agent

By email:

If relating to content on Trulia.com and related websites: DMCA_notice_email@trulia.com

Otherwise: [DMCA_notice_email@zillow.com](mailto:DMCA_notice_email@zillow.com)

If you give notice of copyright infringement by e-mail, we may begin investigating the alleged copyright infringement; however, we must receive your signed statement by mail or as an attachment to your e-mail before we are required to take any action.

  13. **Termination/Changes to Agreement**. Except as stated in separate product-specific agreements, you may terminate your account at any time by contacting [consumercare@zillow.com](mailto:consumercare@zillow.com). If you terminate your account, you remain obligated to pay all outstanding fees, if any, incurred prior to termination relating to your use of the Services. If you violate any provision of these Terms of Use, your permission from Zillow Group to use the Services will terminate automatically. In addition, Zillow Group may in its sole discretion terminate your account on the Services or suspend or terminate your access to the Services at any time for any reason, with or without notice. Zillow Group may alter, suspend or discontinue the Services or any portion of the Services without notice. Zillow Group will not be liable whatsoever for any change to the Services or any suspension or termination of your access to or use of the Services. Zillow Group reserves the right to change these Terms of Use at any time in its sole discretion on a going-forward basis. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of any material changes to these Terms of Use. Your continued use of the Services after updates are effective will represent your agreement to the revised version of these Terms of Use. Your continued use of the Services after the effectiveness of such changes will constitute acceptance of and agreement to any such changes. You further waive any right you may have to receive specific notice of such changes to these Terms of Use. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these Terms of Use.
  14. **Privacy Policy/Other Terms.**
    1. **Privacy Policy**. Zillow Group will collect, use, store, and disclose personal information in accordance with its Privacy Policy. Please consult the [Privacy Policy](https://www.zillow.com/corp/Privacy.htm) for more information, which is incorporated into, and made a part of, these Terms of Use.
    2. **Other Terms**. Your use of the Services is subject to all additional guidelines, rules, and agreements applicable to the Services or certain features of the Services that we may post on, or link to, from the Services, such as rules applicable to a particular product or content available through the Services, including, without limitation, the [Good Neighbor Policy](https://www.zillow.com/howto/GoodNeighborPolicy.htm), the [Listing Quality Policy](http://www.zillow.com/corp/Quality.htm), the [Zillow Group Marketplace Terms of Use](http://www.zillow.com/mortgage/help/TermsOfUse.htm), the [Rentals User Terms](https://www.zillow.com/renter-hub/terms/Rental-User-Terms), and the [Video Walkthrough Guidelines](http://www.zillow.com/wikipages/Video-Walkthrough-Guidelines/). If you are a non-affiliated Lender and participate in any Services offered by Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc. you are also subject to the Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc. [Terms of Use](https://www.zillow.com/mortgage/help/TermsOfUse.htm). All such terms are incorporated into, and made a part of, these Terms of Use.
  15. **Indemnification.** You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Zillow Group, its affiliates, and their respective directors, officers, employees, and agents from any and all claims and demands made by any third party due to or arising out of: (a) your access to or use of the Services; (b) your breach of these Terms of Use; (c) your violation of any law or the rights of a third party; (d) any dispute or issue between you and any third party; (e) any User Materials you upload to, or otherwise make available through, the Services; (f) your willful misconduct; and (g) any other party’s access to and/or use of the Services using your account and password. Zillow Group reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, and in that case, you agree to corporate with Zillow Group’s defense of that claim.
  16. **No Warranties.**  ZILLOW GROUP PROVIDES THE SERVICES “AS IS,” “WITH ALL FAULTS” AND “AS AVAILABLE,” AND THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY, AND EFFORT IS WITH YOU. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ZILLOW GROUP AND ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. ZILLOW GROUP AND ITS SUPPLIERS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS, EXPRESS, STATUTORY AND IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION: (A) WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WORKMANLIKE EFFORT, ACCURACY, TITLE, QUIET ENJOYMENT, NO ENCUMBRANCES, NO LIENS AND NON-INFRINGEMENT; (B) WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS ARISING THROUGH COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE; AND (C) WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE ACCESS OR USE. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SERVICES OR ANY MATERIALS AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICES WILL CREATE ANY WARRANTY REGARDING ANY ZILLOW GROUP ENTITY OR THE SERVICES THAT IS NOT EXPRESSIVELY STATED IN THESE TERMS OF USE. YOU ASSUME ALL RISK FOR ANY DAMAGE THAT MAY RESULT FROM YOUR USE OF OR ACCESS TO THE SERVICES, YOUR DEALING WITH ANY OTHER USER, AND ANY MATERIALS, INCLUDING ALL USER AND ZILLOW GROUP MATERIALS, AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICES. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES, AND USE, ACCESS, DOWNLOAD, OR OTHERWISE OBTAINMENT OF MATERIALS THROUGH THE SERVICES AND ANY ASSOCIATED SITES OR SERVICES, ARE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK, AND THAT YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR PROPERTY (INCLUDING YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR MOBILE DEVICE USED IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICES), OR THE LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE USE OF THE SERVICES OR THE DOWNLOAD OR USE OF THOSE MATERIALS. SOME JURISDICTIONS MAY PROHIBIT A DISCLAIMER OR WARRANTIES AND YOU MAY HAVE OTHER RIGHTS THAT VARY FROM JURSIDICTION TO JURISDICTION.
  17. **Limitation of Liability/Exclusive Remedy.** IN NO EVENT WILL ZILLOW GROUP OR ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, OR ANY OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSS) ARISING OUT OF, BASED ON, OR RESULTING FROM THESE TERMS OF USE OR YOUR USE OR ACCESS, OR INABILITY TO USE OR ACCESS, THE SERVICES OR ANY MATERIALS ON THE SERVICES, WHETHER BASED ON (A) BREACH OF CONTRACT, (B) BREACH OF WARRANTY, (C) NEGLIGENCE, OR (D) ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION, EVEN IF ZILLOW GROUP HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ZILLOW GROUP ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY (E) ERRORS, MISTAKES, OR INACCURACIES OF MATERIALS; (F) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE SERVICES; (G) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED THEREIN; (H) ANY INTERRUPTION OR CESSATION OF TRANSMISSION TO OR FROM THE SERVICES; (I) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE THAT MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH OUR SERVICES BY ANY THIRD PARTY; (J) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY MATERIALS OR FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE INCURRED AS A RESULT OF THE USE OF ANY MATERIALS POSTED, EMAILED, TRANSMITTED, OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICES; AND/OR (K) USER MATERIALS OR THE DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE, OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY. THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF ZILLOW GROUP AND ANY OF ITS AFFILIATES TO YOU FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE ANY PORTION OF THE SERVICES OR OTHERWISE UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE, IS LIMITED TO THE GREATER OF: (L) THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID TO ZILLOW GROUP FOR THE SERVICES IN THE 12 MONTHS PRIOR TO THE EVENTS OR CIRCUMSTANCES GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIMS; AND (B) $100. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. EACH PROVISION OF THESE TERMS OF USE THAT PROVIDES FOR A LIMITATION OF LIABILITY, DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES, OR EXCLUSION OF DAMAGES IS INTENDED TO AND DOES ALLOCATE THE RISKS BETWEEN THE PARTIES UNDER THESE TERMS. THIS ALLOCATION IS AN ESSENTIAL ELEMENT OF THE AGREEMENT OF THE PARTIES. THE LIMITATIONS IN THIS SECTION WILL APPLY EVEN IF ANY LIMITED REMEDY FAILS ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.
  18. **Choice of Law; Disputes.  **These Terms of Use are governed by the laws of the State of Washington, without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions. You agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction and venue in the state and federal courts sitting in King County, Washington for any and all disputes, claims and actions arising from or in connection with the Services and/or these Terms of Use. Zillow Group operates the Services from its offices in Washington, and we make no representation that the Services are appropriate or available for use in other locations.
  19. **General.  **You agree not to export from anywhere any part of the Services provided to you, or any direct product thereof, except in compliance with, and with all licenses and approvals required under, applicable export laws, rules and regulations. All Services used by the U.S. Government are provided with the commercial license rights described herein. These Terms of Use may only be amended by a written agreement signed by authorized representatives of the parties to these Terms of Use. If any part of these Terms of Use is determined to be invalid or unenforceable, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be replaced with a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of these Terms of Use will continue in effect. The section titles in these Terms of Use are solely used for the convenience of the parties and have no legal or contractual significance. Zillow Group may assign this Agreement, in whole or in part, at any time with or without notice to you. You may not assign these Terms of Use, or assign, transfer or sublicense your rights, if any, in the Services. Zillow Group’s failure to act with respect to a breach by you or others does not waive its right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches. Except as expressly stated herein, these Terms of Use, and all expressly incorporated terms and agreements, constitute the entire agreement between you and Zillow Group with respect to the Services and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications of any kind between you and Zillow Group with respect to the Services. The following sections of these Terms of Use shall survive any termination of these Terms of Use: 4, 6-9, 11-13, and 15-23.
  20. **Consent to Communications**. By using the Services, you consent to receiving certain electronic communications from Zillow Group as further described in the Privacy Policy. Please read the Privacy Policy to learn more. You agree that any notices, agreements, disclosures, or other communications that Zillow Group sends to you electronically will satisfy any legal communication requirements, including that those communications be in writing. The Services may provide web forms, links, or contact information, including phone numbers, that can connect you with Zillow Group or third parties, such as real estate agents and Third-Party Providers. Communications through these methods may be routed through a third-party service (“Communications Service”). Calls may be recorded or monitored for quality assurance and customer service purposes. You will be notified at the beginning of a call if it may be recorded or monitored. You consent to such recording and monitoring by Zillow Group or the Communications Service. Zillow Group also uses the Communications Service to track phone calls and text messages between you and real estate professionals so that Zillow Group and the real estate professional can access certain details about the contact.  As part of this process, Zillow Group and the Communications Service will receive in real time, and store, data about your call or text message, including the date and time of the call or text message, your phone number, and the content of the text message. You consent to these practices by Zillow Group and the Communications Service. The information is subject to the Privacy Policy.
  21. **Notice to California Residents**. If you are a California resident, under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, you may contact the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of the California Department of Consumer Affairs in writing at 1625 N. Market Blvd., Suite S-202, Sacramento, California 95834, or by telephone at (800) 952-5210 in order to resolve a complaint regarding the Service or to receive further information regarding use of the Service.
  22. **Contact Information and License Disclosures**. The Services are offered by Zillow, Inc. and its affiliates, located at 1301 Second Avenue, Floor 31, Seattle, WA 98101. You may contact Zillow Group by sending correspondence to that address or emailing [consumercare@zillow.com](mailto:consumercare@zillow.com). To see a complete list of Zillow, Inc.’s real estate brokerage licenses, see [Real Estate Licenses](https://www.zillow.com/info/real-estate-licenses/). Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc. is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Zillow, Inc. and has its headquarters at 1301 Second Ave., Fl. 31, Seattle, Washington 98101. The Nationwide Mortgage Licensing System (NMLS) Identification Number for Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc. is 1303160. To see a complete list of Zillow Group Marketplace, Inc.’s licenses, see [Licensing and Disclosures](https://www.zillow.com/mortgage/help/license-disclosures/). Zillow, Inc. indirectly owns a membership interest in ZHL. ZHL has its headquarters at 10975 El Monte, Overland Park, KS 66211. The NMLS Identification Number for ZHL is 10287. To see a complete list of ZHL’s licenses, see [Licensing](https://www.zillowhomeloans.com/licensing).
  23. **Notice to Apple Users**. If you are using our mobile applications on an iOS device, the terms of this Section 23 apply. You acknowledge that these Terms of Use are between you and Zillow Group only, not with Apple, and Apple is not responsible for the Services or related Materials. Apple has no obligation to furnish any maintenance or support services with respect to the Services. If the Services fail to conform to any applicable warranty, you may notify Apple and Apple will refund any applicable purchase price for the mobile application to you; and, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, Apple has no other warranty obligation with respect to the Services. Apple is not responsible for addressing any claim by you or any third party relating to the Services or your possession or use of the Services, including: (a) product liability claims; (b) any claim that the Services fail to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement; and (c) claims arising under consumer protection or similar legislation. Apple is not responsible for the investigation, defense, settlement or discharge of any third-party claim that the Services or your possession and use of the mobile application infringe that third party’s intellectual property rights. You agree to comply with any applicable third-party terms when using the Services. Apple and Apple’s subsidiaries are third party beneficiaries of Section 23 of these Terms of Use, and upon your acceptance of these Terms or Use, Apple will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce this Section 23 of these Terms of Use against you. You hereby represent and warrant that: (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a “terrorist supporting” country; and (ii) you are not listed on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.

**Last Updated:** 6/25/2019

At Zillow Group, we appreciate your use of and contributions to our websites, our mobile and desktop applications, our other properties and/or our related services (collectively known as the “Services,” or, each individually, a “Service”). Zillow Group respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information.

We encourage you to read this privacy policy to understand the information we collect and how we use and disclose it.  This policy applies to all of our Services that link to it.

**1\. Information Collected by Zillow Group**

When you use the Services, we collect a variety of information from and about you, your devices, and your interaction with the Services.  Some of this information identifies you directly or can be used to identify you when combined with other data.

  * **Information you provide.** When using the Services, you may be asked to provide personal information about yourself, such as your name, contact information, payment information, details about your home or properties you are interested in, financial information. This may occur, for example, when you register on the Services, claim a home, share or save a property, correspond with a real estate professional (such as a real estate agent or broker, mortgage lender or loan officer, property manager, investor, homebuilder, or others) via the Services, or complete other forms or transactions, such as a request for loan information or a rental housing and background check application. You may also provide information about a third party through the Services, for example, if you share a real estate listing with a recipient via email. We may combine this information with other information we collect from your interaction with the Services or from other companies.Some information you provide through the Services is collected and processed by third parties on our behalf.  For example, when you order products or services through the Services, we may need to collect your credit or debit card information. This information is collected and processed by third-party payment processors.  In the event that a credit report is required to use a Service, you may be asked to provide your Social Security number (“SSN”). When SSNs are required, we use technology to pass that information directly to the third-party providers who need the information to process the credit or background check report. If you are a real estate professional, you may be able to connect your third-party email account (such as Gmail) to your Zillow Group account.  If you enable that connection, Zillow Group will access your messages, contacts, and settings to provide the requested Services to you.
  * **Cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.** We and our partners use various technologies to collect information automatically when you access and use the Services, including cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies. Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to your computer or other electronic device to uniquely identify your browser. When you use the Services, we and our partners may place one or more cookies on your computer or other electronic device or use other technologies that provide similar functionality.  We and our partners may use cookies to connect your activity on the Services with other information we store about you in your account profile or your prior interactions on the Services to, for example, store your preferences. The use of cookies helps us improve the quality of the Services to you, by identifying information which is most interesting to you, tracking trends, measuring the effectiveness of advertising, or storing information you may want to retrieve on a regular basis, such as your favorite homes. At any time, you may adjust settings on your browser to refuse cookies according to the instructions related to your browser. However, if you choose to disable cookies, many of the free features of the Services will not operate properly.The pages on the Services may also include web beacons or pixels, which are electronic files to count users who have visited that page, to track activity over time and across different websites, to determine users’ interactions with emails we send, to identify certain cookies on the computer or other electronic device accessing that page, or to collect other related information, and this information may be associated with your unique browser, device identifier, or Internet Protocol address. We may, for example, implement a pixel on the pages of the Services where you view a certain advertisement so that we can track whether you visit a website associated with that advertisement at a later time. **   **
  * **Third-party cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.** We work with service providers and advertising networks to track and manage cookie information and your activities while you’re using the Services and your online activities over time and across different websites and devices. For example, third parties may use cookies to deliver advertisements to you based on your visit to the Services. For additional information, please refer to the section below entitled, “Interest-Based Advertising.” You may opt-out of cookie tracking and analysis from any of these service providers and advertising networks by [Opting Out of Collection of Information](http://www.zillow.com/corp/Privacy.htm#optOut) _by Third Parties_ , which is explained further below.
  * **Mobile device and mobile browser information.  **You may adjust settings on your mobile device and mobile browser regarding cookies and sharing of certain information, such as your mobile device model or the language your mobile device uses, by adjusting the privacy and security settings on your mobile device.  Please refer to the instructions provided by your mobile service provider or mobile device manufacturer.
  * **Location Data**. If you enable location services on your mobile device, Zillow Group may collect the location of your device, which we use to provide you with location-based information and advertising. If you wish to deactivate this feature, you can disable location services on your mobile device.
  * **Usage logs.  **We collect information about your use of our Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services. We also collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, such as the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information, and browsing behavior.
  * **Calls and text messages.** Calls between you and Zillow Group, or between you and third parties made through Zillow Group (such as real estate agents you contact about a property through a form or link on our website, or using contact information found on our website), may be recorded or monitored for quality assurance and customer service purposes. You will be notified at the beginning of a call if it may be recorded or monitored.  Zillow Group uses a third-party service provider to track phone calls and text messages between you and real estate professionals so that we and the real estate professional can access certain details about the contact.  As part of this process, Zillow Group and its service provider will receive in real time and store data about your call or text message, including the date and time of the call or text message, your phone number, and the content of the text message.
  * **Public content**. You may provide information publicly through the Services, such as when you leave a review for a real estate professional, or when you contribute to discussion forums.
  * **Social networks**.  If you use the social networking connection functions offered through the Services, we may access all of your social network profile information that you have made available to be shared and to use it in accordance with this privacy policy.  Please refer to the instructions governing your social network account to manage the information that is shared through your account.

**Collection of information by third-party services**. Some Services require collection of your information directly by third parties. For example, if you use the Services to make rent payments, Zillow Group uses Plaid Inc. (“Plaid”) to collect your personal and financial information about you from financial institutions. By using such Services, you grant Zillow Group and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution. Your personal and financial information will be transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/legal).

Zillow Group will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13.

**2\. How Zillow Group Uses Your Information**

Zillow Group generally uses the information collected about you to provide and improve the Services, including to:

  * provide and deliver the Services, process transactions and send related information such as confirmations and invoices;
  * send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by Zillow Group and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * revise, modify, and update existing Services and develop new Services;
  * detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Zillow Group and others;
  * personalize the Services and present you with advertising, content or features that we believe will be of interest or useful to you;
  * facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;
  * link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information was collected.

**Email Management.   **You may receive email from Zillow Group for a variety of reasons – for example, if you took an action through the Services, you signed up for a regular report, or you posted your home for sale and a buyer sent you a message. If you have an account with Zillow Group, you can select your preferences through your account settings. Also, you can manage your receipt of some types of communication by following the instructions included in the email we send you. Please note that, even if you unsubscribe from certain email correspondences, we may still need to email you with important transactional or administrative information.

**3\. When Zillow Group Shares and Discloses Your Information**

Your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting your information that identifies you personally. We will only share personal information that you provide outside the public areas of the Services in the following circumstances:

  * **With your consent.** When you consent or direct Zillow Group to share the personal information. This happens when you submit your information through many of our Services.  For example, if you choose to contact a real estate agent, mortgage lender, investor, builder, property manager, or other real estate professional through the Services, your name, phone number, email address, and message content will appear to the recipient of the message.  Similarly, if you apply for rental housing through the Services, your application information will be sent to prospective landlords.
  * **Service providers to Zillow  Group. **When Zillow Group hires a service provider to help operate the Services or our business, Zillow Group may give access to personal information only as appropriate to perform the service for Zillow Group, and subject to the terms of this privacy policy.  Zillow Group always remains responsible for the privacy of your personal information that is shared with service providers.
  * **Partners with whom we conduct business**. When Zillow Group partners with other businesses to offer products and services, we may share information with those business partners only as needed to provide those products and services and only subject to the terms of this privacy policy.
  * **Legal obligation or protection from harm.** When Zillow Group has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any requirement of law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce or investigate a potential violation of the Terms of Use, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise respond to fraud, security or technical concerns, (d) support auditing and compliance functions, or (e) protect the rights, property, or safety of Zillow Group, its users, or the public against harm.
  * **Business transfers.** If and when Zillow Group is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of transfer or sale of some or all of its business, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, we may share your personal information in connection with that transaction.

Zillow Group may also share aggregated or de-identified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

**4\. Interest-Based Advertising**

We participate in interest-based advertising. This means that when you use the Services, we or third party service providers or advertisers may use cookies (that they collect or that we provide to them) or other similar technologies to collect information about your use of the Services (including mobile applications) or your online activities over time and across different websites and devices. Collected information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, and the website that referred you to the Services, and this information may be associated with your unique browser, device identifier, or Internet Protocol (IP) address. These practices help tailor advertisements that are relevant and useful to you. These tailored advertisements may appear on the Services or on other websites, applications or properties.

In addition, if you have provided your email address to us, we may use a scrambled, unreadable form (a hash) of your email address to deliver tailored advertisements to you on the Services or on other websites, including via Facebook’s Custom Audience Feature or other similar tools. Click [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#types) to learn about how you can control the ads you see on Facebook. We do not access or collect any of the contents of your email messages in providing interest-based advertising.  Our use of information received from Gmail APIs will adhere to [Google’s Limited Use Requirements](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional-requirements-for-specific-api-scopes).

You may opt-out of cookie tracking and analysis as described in the section below entitled ‘Opting Out of Collection of Information by Third Parties’. The Services do not otherwise respond to ‘do not track’ signals.

**5\. Opting Out of Collection of Information by Third Parties**

Zillow Group’s third-party ad servers, ad network providers, third-party advertisers may provide you with advertisements that you may see on the Services or on other affiliated websites. To improve the relevancy and help measure the effectiveness of such advertisements, the Zillow Group Ad Providers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies. These are used to record users’ activity, such as the pages visited, and to learn what types of information are of most interest to the users. For more information regarding the choices you have about these technologies (such as opting-out), visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), [Omniture](https://www.d1.sc.omtrdc.net/optout.html), and [PrivacyChoice](http://privacychoice.org/trackerblock).

**6\. Third-Party Links and Websites**

Throughout the Services, we may link to the websites of other companies and/or individuals. Further, certain functionalities on the Services may involve the distribution of your listing information to third-party websites. These third-party websites may collect information about users on those websites, and Zillow Group’s privacy policy does not extend to these external websites and third parties. Please refer directly to these third parties and websites regarding their privacy policies.

**7\. Security and Retention of Information**

Zillow Group takes reasonable steps to protect the information users share with us from unauthorized use, access, and disclosure, both during transmission and at rest. However, no transmission of information via the Internet nor electronic storage solution can be entirely secure, so please be aware that we cannot guarantee absolute security.

You can access, update, and delete personal information you provide to Zillow Group in your account profile by logging into your account on the relevant Zillow Group Service. We may maintain a copy of the original version of your information in our records.

We will retain your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

**8\. Transfer of Information to the United States**

Zillow Group is based in the United States and you acknowledge that the information we collect is governed by U.S. law.  By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer, and storage of information in and to the United States, where you may not have the same rights and protections as you do under local law.

**9\. Government and Private Party Information Requests**

Zillow Group occasionally receives various forms of legal process from government agencies and private parties requesting information about Zillow Group users.  Before we produce information, we will attempt to notify affected users and give them an opportunity to object unless notification is prohibited by law or if we believe that notification would create a risk of harm or be otherwise counterproductive.

**10\. Contacting Zillow Group**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the privacy practices of Zillow Group, please email us at [privacy@zillow.com](mailto:privacy@zillow.com), or you can write to us at:

Zillow Group, Inc.  
Attn: Consumer Care  
1301 Second Avenue, Floor 31  
Seattle, WA 98101

**11\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this policy may be amended from time to time. You should check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy. We will provide notice of material changes to the policy, either by posting a notice on our websites, by sending an email, or some other reasonable method.

## Privacy Policy (Effective Jan. 1, 2020)

**Effective Date:** January 1, 2020

When you use Zillow Group services to find, buy, rent, or sell your home, get a mortgage, or connect to a real estate pro, we know you’re trusting us with your data. We also know we have a responsibility to respect your privacy, and we work hard to do just that.  This policy explains what information we collect, why we use it, who we share it with, and how we protect it, along with the tools you can use to manage your privacy.

### Introduction

### Information collected by Zillow

### Why Zillow uses your information

### Sharing your information

### Privacy tools and choices

### Protecting your information

### Applicability of this policy

### Legal disclosures

### Contacting Zillow 

### Changes to this policy

We offer a wide range of services that focus on all stages of the home lifecycle: renting, buying, selling, financing, and home improvement.

We know that everyone’s home journey is different, and that deciding on the right place to call home is an intimate, personal experience.  Along with a wealth of information about homes, neighborhoods, market conditions, local real estate professionals, and financing options, we also use the information you give us to provide our services and help you find your next home.

We carefully evaluate how we use data to make sure that we’re using your information to provide value **for you**.  On this page, we aim to explain everything you need to know about your privacy at Zillow.   If you have any questions that we haven’t answered here, you can always contact us at [privacy@zil](mailto:privacy@zillow.com)[low.com](mailto:privacy@zillow.com).

When you use our services, we collect a variety of information from and about you and your devices.  Some of this information identifies you directly (like an email address) while some of it is associated with you through your account, profile, or device (like the homes you choose to save or your location data).

The kind of data we collect about you depends on how you use Zillow.  If you only use our services to browse for homes, we’ll have less information about you than if we help you [sell your home](https://www.zillow.com/offers/), [get a mortgage](https://www.zillow.com/home-loans/), [sign your lease](https://www.zillow.com/rent/guide/), or if you use any of our other transaction services.  Even if you don’t have an account with us, we may still collect some data about you, like your email address and phone number if you choose to contact a real estate agent through our platform, or your IP address and other device information when you browse our sites or use our apps.

## Information you give us or create using our services

When you use our services, we often ask you for information about yourself.  This usually includes basic things like your name, email address, and phone number.  If you use our transaction services, we might ask you for more sensitive data like your income, housing history, and credit score.  If you contribute information, such as agent reviews, we’ll store that as well.

You may also provide information about other people through our services. For example, if you share a home listing with someone, we will collect that person’s email address as part of your account information.

Below are some examples of what information we collect for our main products and services and how we collect it.

**Zillow Offers**

Zillow Offers extends cash offers on residential real estate in select U.S. cities.  If you ask for an offer on your home, we will ask you for information about you and your home. This includes contact information (such as an email address or phone number), identifying information about you, and details about your home.  We may also take some photos of your home so we know what types of repairs may be necessary.  If we agree to buy your home, we’ll need to collect more information from you that is typical of any real estate transaction, including financial information.

We collect similar contact and transaction-related information from you if you are interested in purchasing a Zillow-owned home.  If you choose to tour a Zillow-owned home, we collect information to verify your identity.  Zillow may collect information about you from third parties if needed to verify your identity.

**Home Search**

When you use Zillow’s home search brands (including Zillow, Trulia, HotPads, StreetEasy, NakedApartments, and OutEast) to find a home to buy or rent, we give you lots of tools to find your next home.  If you tell us what you’re looking for, such as the type of home or number of bedrooms, we save that information so that we can tailor your search results to what you’re looking for.

We also help you connect with local real estate agents, homebuilders, property managers, mortgage loan officers, and other real estate professionals.  If you choose to contact one of these pros through our platform, we ask for your name, email address, and phone number so that we can reach you and connect you with the right person.

You can also claim your home on Zillow and edit home facts such as the square footage, number of bathrooms, and most recent renovation year.  We link the information you provide to your account.

**Rental Tools**

You can use Zillow to apply for rental housing, sign your lease, and even pay your rent.  When you choose to use these features, we collect information from you to process your transaction.

During the rental application process, we collect your information like your email address and phone number, employment history, rental history, income, and credit score.  You can use our tools to pull your credit report and criminal background check to include in your application, but Zillow doesn’t store your Social Security number and we don’t collect or see the credit or background check reports. We partner with Experian and Checkr to generate those reports and make them available only to you and the landlords you choose to send them to.

When you pay your rent through Zillow, we collect your transaction information, but we don’t store your payment account details.  Instead, we use trusted partners to collect and store that data.  If you use your bank account to pay your rent, our service provider Plaid collects personal and financial information from your bank or other financial institution. By using Zillow to make your rent payments, you are granting Zillow and Plaid the right, power, and authority to act on your behalf to access and transmit your personal and financial information from the relevant financial institution. Your information will be transferred, stored, and processed by Plaid in accordance with the [Plaid Privacy Policy](https://plaid.com/legal).

If you sign your lease documents through Zillow, we will collect and store your contact information, signature, and any other information contained in the lease documents, which can vary by state and city.

**Zillow Home Loans**

This privacy policy does not apply to Zillow Home Loans.  To understand what kind of information Zillow Home Loans collects, please read the [Zillow Home Loans Privacy Policy](https://www.zillowhomeloans.com/privacy).

### Services and Products for Professionals

If you are a real estate professional, you may be able to connect your third-party email account (such as Gmail) to your Zillow account.  If you enable that connection, Zillow will access your messages, contacts, and settings only to provide the requested services to you.  We do not access or collect any of the contents of your email messages in providing interest-based advertising.  We use information received from Gmail APIs only in compliance with [Google’s Limited Use Requirements](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional-requirements-for-specific-api-scopes).

We also collect your contact and payment details, along with professional information such as brokerage affiliation, associated listings and sales, and licensing history.

### Information from Public Sources and Third Parties

Zillow collects information from public sources, such as county and state tax and property records, government agencies, and multiple listing services (or MLS).  Most of this information is about properties, not people.  But some information we collect, like the identity of a property’s owner or real estate license information, may relate to individuals.

We also collect information about you from various third parties in order to provide better service to you, or as part of the employment application process.  This may include demographic information and other attributes about you.

## Information we collect as you use our services

Along with the information you give us directly, we collect a variety of information automatically as you use Zillow services.

### Activity information

We collect information about how you use Zillow.  This includes things like your home search history, homes you view, purchase activity, what you’ve clicked on and other uses of our features, and the amount of time you spend looking at different parts of our websites.  When you call or text Zillow or a real estate professional using our platform, we collect data about your call or text, including the date and time of the call or text, your phone number, and the content of the call or text.

### Device information

Like other websites and apps, we collect data about the browsers and devices you use to access Zillow.  The data we collect includes browser or device model and settings, operating system, unique identifiers, and the version of the app you’re using. We also collect data about how your browsers and devices interact with our services, including IP address, crash reports, system activity, and the date, time, and the URL of the site you visited before Zillow.

You can control our collection of certain data, such as your mobile device model or the language your mobile device uses, by adjusting the privacy and security settings on your mobile device.

### Location Information

If you enable location services on your mobile device, Zillow collects the location of your device.  We use that information to provide you with location-based information and ads, like homes and real estate professionals in your area, and to offer location-based services, like allowing you to unlock and tour Zillow Offers homes on your own schedule and claiming your home on Zillow.  If you don’t want to use these features, you can turn off location services on your device.

We also collect location information for similar purposes from your browser if you enable it.  You can disable access through your browser settings.

**Cookies, pixel tags, and other tracking technologies**

We and our partners use various tools to collect data when you visit our sites and apps, including cookies, pixel tags, and other similar technologies. Cookies are bits of electronic data that can be transferred to your computer or other device to identify your browser.

When you use Zillow, we and our partners may use cookies and other tools to gather information about how you view and use our services and content, and to connect your activity with other data we store about you. The use of cookies helps us serve you better by understanding what you’re interested in, tracking trends, measuring the effectiveness of ads, saving your preferences, and storing information you may want to retrieve on a regular basis, such as your favorite homes. We also allow specific, approved partners to collect data from your browser or device for advertising and measurement purposes using their own cookies or similar tools.

At any time, you can use our cookie preference tools to manage what kinds of cookies and other tracking technologies you’re comfortable with.  Check out our for information about how to access these tools.  You can also disable cookies altogether by adjusting the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable some or all cookies, many parts of our services may no longer work.  **   **

In addition, if you give your email address to us, we may use a scrambled, unreadable form (called a “hashed” version) of your email address to deliver tailored ads to you on Zillow or on other websites, including via Facebook’s Custom Audience Feature or other similar tools. Click [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/#types) to learn about how you can control the ads you see on Facebook.

For information about how you can manage your cookie preferences, check out the section of this policy called “Your privacy tools and choices.”

### Social networks

If you use social media logins (like Google and Facebook) to log in to Zillow, we may access your public social media profile information.  You can always limit this sharing using your social media service settings.

### Inferences

To improve our services and make them more useful to you, we use data about your activity to understand and infer your preferences.  For example, if you usually search for homes for rent rather than homes to buy, we may assume that you are not looking to buy a home and show you more information helpful for renters.

### Commercial Information

We collect information about the products and services you purchase or consider purchasing from us.  This includes products for professionals, such as our advertising products, as well as consumer services like Zillow Offers.

**Audiovisual information**

If you visit a home owned by Zillow, we may capture your likeness and voice using cameras and audio recording equipment for safety reasons.

## Completing your transactions

When you use Zillow to complete real estate transactions, like buying or selling your home, applying to rental housing, or signing a lease, we use your personal information to verify your identity and process and complete your transaction.

## Providing and improving our services

We use your information to provide our services to you. This includes things like returning home search results and processing your rental application.  We also use your information to improve our existing services and develop new ones.  For example, we track how you use our websites and apps and use that information to troubleshoot issues and adjust things to improve your experience.

## Communicating with you and connecting you with others

We use the contact information you provide us, like your phone number and email address, to communicate with you about our services.  This includes things like responding to comments, questions, and requests you send us. It also includes notifying you of transaction or service updates and changes.  We may also inform you about our services, offers, promotions, news, and other updates we think may be of interest to you.

If you ask us to, we also use your information to connect you to real estate professionals, like when you want to contact an agent to discuss a home you find for sale on our platform.

## Personalizing your experience

We use the information we collect about you and your activity on our services to personalize the services we offer.  We also use it to show advertising, content, or features that we think you might like.  This includes things like customized search results that match your preferences and prior search criteria and, if you ask us to, connecting you to a real estate professional best suited to help you.

If we know you’re working with a particular real estate agent, we may share information about your saved homes and searches with that agent to let them serve you more effectively.  You control what we share with real estate pros you find on our platform.

## Other uses of your information

We also use your data to detect, investigate, and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and to protect the rights and property of Zillow, its customers, and others.

Occasionally, there may be a reason we’d like to use your information in a way that isn’t described here.  If that happens, we’ll let you know so you can decide if you’re comfortable with it.

We understand that sharing information with third parties is a big responsibility.  We’re committed to sharing information only when needed for a legitimate business or legal purpose, and then only with recipients who will protect it.

## Information you ask us to share

We share information when you ask us to share it. For example, if you choose to contact a real estate agent, mortgage lender, investor, builder, property manager, or other real estate pro through our platform, we will send them your name and contact information. Similarly, if you apply for rental housing through Zillow, your application information will be sent to the landlords you select.

## Service providers and business partners

When Zillow hires a service provider to help operate our business, we may need to give them access to information to provide their service.  We allow them to use the information only to perform the service we’ve asked them to perform.  We vet all service providers carefully, and Zillow always remains responsible for the privacy of your information that is shared with our service providers.

When Zillow partners with other businesses to offer products and services to you, we may share information with those partners only as needed to provide those products and services and only subject to the terms of this privacy policy.

## Legal and compliance transfers

When Zillow needs to share data to satisfy a legal or regulatory requirement, including responding to a subpoena or other lawful government request for data, we will share information only as necessary to comply with that requirement.  We’ll tell you before sharing your information in these situations unless we’re prohibited from doing so.  For more information about how we respond to requests for data, see [Government and Civil Information Requests](https://www.zillowgroup.com/terms-of-use-privacy-policy/government-civil-information-requests/).  We may also share information if needed to enforce our legal rights, detect or prevent fraud or security concerns, and protect public safety.

If Zillow is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of transfer or sale of some or all of its business, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, we may share your information in connection with that transaction.

## Public and deidentified data

We may share information that is collected from public sources or that you choose to share publicly (such as public reviews and home facts) with third parties.  We may also share aggregated and/or deidentified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

## Sales of personal information

Zillow allows certain companies to place tracking technologies like cookies and pixels on our sites, which allow those companies to receive information about your activity on Zillow that is associated with your browser or device.  The companies may use that data to serve you more relevant ads on our sites or others.  Under some state laws, sharing data for online advertising like this may be considered a “sale” of information.  Except for this kind of sharing, Zillow doesn’t sell any of your information.

You always have full control over whether these technologies work on your devices.  You can disable them entirely using our cookie consent preference tools (see the Zillow Privacy Center for instructions), or by clicking the “Do Not Sell My Information” link on our websites.

## Accessing and deleting your information

We’ve made a variety of privacy tools available on Zillow.  Using the Zillow Privacy Center, you can see what kind of data we’ve collected about you and the types of third parties we share it with.  You can also download a copy of the data and take it with you to a service outside of Zillow if you want. If you’d like to delete your data or close your account, you can do that using the Zillow Privacy Center as well.

We provide these tools for your benefit and we will never discriminate against you for using them. But if you choose to delete your data or close your account, we won’t be able to offer you services that require us to use your data.

## Managing cookie preferences

The Zillow [Privacy Center](https://privacy.zillowgroup.com/) has information about how to use tools on our websites and apps to manage what kinds of cookies are allowed to load when you use Zillow.

Zillow’s third-party ad servers, ad network providers, and third-party advertisers provide ad content that appears on Zillow. To measure how effective those ads are and to make them more relevant, ad providers may use their own tracking technologies to collect your information. These are used to record users’ activity, such as the pages visited, and to learn what types of information are of most interest to the users. For more information regarding the choices you have about these technologies (such as opting out), visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), [Omniture](https://www.d1.sc.omtrdc.net/optout.html), and [PrivacyChoice](http://privacychoice.org/trackerblock).

## Managing communications preferences

### Email subscriptions

Zillow may send you email for a variety of reasons.  For example, if you save a search, we’ll send you emails with new homes on the market that match your search.  If you save a home, we’ll keep you posted on status updates like when that home has an open house scheduled and when it has an offer pending.  When you use our transaction services, we’ll send you status updates and other information about your transaction.  If you have an account with Zillow, you can select your preferences through your account settings. Also, you can manage the types of email you receive by following the instructions included in each email we send you. Even if you unsubscribe from some email subscriptions, we may still need to email you with important transactional or other non-advertising information.

### Calls and texts

Some of our services allow you to provide your phone number to us.  If you give us your number, we may call or text you, for example, to give you information about getting an offer on your home through Zillow Offers. We will contact you through these methods only in accordance with applicable legal requirements, and you always have the ability to opt out of further calls or texts.

We understand that no matter how we collect your information, we have a responsibility to protect it.  We take that responsibility seriously.  We build security into our products and features from the ground up to help protect data from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

We’re always looking for threats and take reasonable steps to respond to those threats, protecting the information users share with us.  Of course, no method of Internet transmission or data storage can provide guaranteed protection to your information.  If anything should ever happen to your information, we’ll let you know as soon as we can and try our best to make it right.

Zillow is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed primarily by U.S. law.  Where we are subject to the privacy laws of other countries, we comply with those requirements.  If you access or use our services or provide information to us, your information will be processed and stored in the United States, where you may not have the same rights and protections as you do under your local law.

This policy applies to every service of ours that links to it.  It does not apply to Zillow Home Loans, which has a separate privacy policy available [here](https://www.zillowhomeloans.com/privacy).

Our apps and services may link to other companies’ websites. Some features may also involve the sharing of your information with third-party websites. These third-party websites may collect information about users on those websites.  Zillow doesn’t control those sites, and this privacy policy does not apply to these external websites and third parties.

In this section, we’ve provided some legally required disclosures under state privacy laws.  There shouldn’t be anything surprising in this section, and we’ve tried to explain our privacy practices in plain English throughout the rest of the policy.

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act or CCPA, California residents have certain rights regarding their data, including:

  * The right to know the categories of personal information we’ve collected and the categories of sources from which we got the information (see Information collected by Zillow and the chart just below)
  * The right to know the business purposes for sharing personal information (see Why Zillow uses your information)
  * The right to know the categories of third parties with whom we’ve shared personal information (see Sharing your information)
  * The right to access the specific pieces of personal information we’ve collected and the right to delete your information (see Privacy tools and choices)

California residents also have the right to not be discriminated against if they choose to exercise their privacy rights.

**Categories of Personal Information under the California Consumer Privacy Act**  
---  
**_Category and sources of Information_** | **_How we use it_** | **_Types of individuals affected_** | **_How we share it_**  
**Identifiers**

We collect this information from our users, customers, and business partners.  We also generate identifiers internally.

| To enable use of our sites, services, and products, to communicate with you, to understand how our users interact with our sites, and to improve our offerings | People who use our sites or mobile applications; create a user account; receive a Zillow Offer; send us an inquiry about buying a home, product, or service from us; ask to be connected to a real estate pro; purchase advertising from us; 

obtain a service from us; and real estate pros who we connect with users

| We share this data with our service providers and with business partners, including those to whom you instruct us to send this information  
**Personal information under**[ **California Civil Code section 1798.80**](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displaySection.xhtml?sectionNum=1798.80.&lawCode=CIV)

We collect this information from our users, customers, and business partners

| To enable use of our sites, services, and products, to communicate with you, to understand how our users interact with our sites, and to improve our offerings | People who create a user account; receive a Zillow Offer; send us an inquiry about buying a home, product, or service from us; ask to be connected to a real estate pro; purchase advertising from us; obtain a service from us; and real estate pros who we connect with users | We share this data with our service providers and with business partners, including those to whom you instruct us to send this information  
**Protected classifications**

We collect this information from our users and business partners

| To understand how our users interact with our sites, and to conduct research into housing and real estate trends and markets | People who buy or sell a home from/to us; use our rental application submission service; enter into a business partnership with us; | We don’t share  
**Commercial information**

We collect this information from our customers, and generate it internally during transactions with our customers

| To transact with you if you use our services or products, and to enable transactions you’ve requested | People who sell us a home; buy a home, product or service from us; purchase advertising from us | We share this data with our service providers and with business partners, including those to whom you instruct us to send this information  
**Biometric information** | We don’t collect this data | None | None  
**Electronic network activity information**

We collect this information from our users and customers

| To enable use of our sites, services, and products, to communicate with you, to understand how our users interact with our sites, and to improve our offerings | People who use our sites or mobile applications | We share this data with our service providers and with business partners, including those to whom you instruct us to send this information  
**Geolocation data**

We collect this information from our users and customers

| To enable use of our sites, services, and products, to understand how our users interact with our sites, and to improve our offerings | People who use our sites or mobile applications and allow us to collect their location data | We share this data with our service providers  
**Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information**

We collect this information from our users and customers

| To identify you, to enable use of our sites, services, and products, and for safety purposes | People who call us; visit or tour a Zillow-owned home | We share this data with our service providers  
**Professional or employment-related information**

We collect this information from our customers and business partners

| To provide services or products you’ve requested | People who use our rental application services; contact us in a business-to-business context; obtain a mortgage loan from us; buy a home from us |  We share this data with our service providers and with business partners, including those to whom you instruct us to send this information  
**Education information**

We collect this information from our customers

| To provide services or products you’ve requested | People who use our rental application services; obtain a mortgage loan from us; buy a home from us | We share this data with our service providers and with business partners, including those to whom you instruct us to send this information  
**Inferences**

We generate these internally

| To understand how our users interact with our sites, to develop and offer more relevant and useful services and products, and to improve the products and services we offer | People who use our sites or mobile applications, including users who: receive a Zillow Offer; ask to be connected with real estate pros; or apply for a mortgage through us | We don’t share  
  
_While California law applies only to California residents, we believe everyone should have the same privacy rights regardless of where you live.   So our privacy tools are available to all of our users.  You can access these tools through the Zillow Privacy Center_ _._

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the privacy practices of Zillow, please check out the Privacy Support Center  for FAQs and other information.

You can also email us at privacy@zillow.com, or you can write to us at:

Zillow, Inc.  
Attn: Consumer Care  
1301 Second Avenue, Floor 31  
Seattle, WA 98101

We are always reviewing our privacy practices to make sure they comply with this policy.  Sometimes, we’ll need to update the policy to reflect changes in our products, technology, and uses of data. We won’t change the policy in a way that reduces your rights or significantly changes the way we use or share data without telling you ahead of time and giving you a chance to stop using our services if you want.

## Government and Civil Information Requests

This page provides information for law enforcement agencies and private litigants seeking production of Zillow Group user data through legal process.  Our legal team reviews requests for user data carefully to ensure that the request is lawful and valid.  We interpret requests narrowly and will challenge requests that we deem vague, overbroad, or lacking a proper legal basis.

**User Notice Policy**

Before we produce information in response to a request, we will attempt to notify affected users and give them an opportunity to object unless notification is prohibited by law or court order or if we believe that notification would create a risk of harm or be otherwise counterproductive.  Non-disclosure instructions contained in legal requests must cite appropriate authority.

**Government and Law Enforcement Agency Requests**

Zillow Group accepts service of subpoenas, search warrants, and court orders seeking production of documents by email from government and law enforcement agencies.  Requests must be submitted to [legalrequests@zillowgroup.com](mailto:legalrequests@zillowgroup.com) from an official government or law enforcement agency email address.  We will not accept service of legal process sent to this mailbox from non-government or non-law enforcement email addresses.

Requests should be accompanied by information about the agency and specific officer or attorney making the request sufficient to allow Zillow Group to verify the request. Requests must also be facially valid and, if applicable, identify the relevant user(s) with specificity. We require a search warrant based on probable cause to release most user account content.

**Private Party Requests**

Zillow Group accepts civil subpoenas for user data issued by King County Superior Court and the federal courts in Washington state.  All subpoenas issued by civil litigants seeking Zillow Group user information must be served personally on Zillow Group at our headquarters at 1301 Second Avenue, Floor 31, Seattle, Washington, 98101, or on CT Corporation, our registered agent for service of process. Zillow Group does not accept service by mail, fax, or email.

Zillow Group reviews all requests for user data carefully to ensure that a valid legal basis exists for the request and will challenge requests that we deem vague, overbroad, or lacking a proper legal basis. Requests must be facially valid and, if applicable, must identify the relevant user(s) with specificity. Before issuing a subpoena, parties should ensure that the information sought is not already available publicly on Zillow Group websites.
